CURRICULAM VITAE

MD. Ibrahim Khalil.

Address: Royel Gate. Bora Kumira, Sitakunda, Chittagong.

Mobile No 1: 01911-179436

e-mail: www.ibrahimkhalil9436@gamil.com



Career summary:

I am working in KSRM Billet Industries Ltd. Bora Kumira, Sitakunda, in Chittagong as a Sr. technician (Electrical & Automation) from 21/07/2016 to till now and
I have achieved almost 04 years of working experience .(Electrical Erection, Installation and Commissioning work Induction Furnace (IF) 35 Ton (Unit 2).

Employment History:

Total Year of Service: 17 Years

1st Company: Jr. Electrician (13/02/2005 to 30/03/2008).

Baizid Newsprint Mills Ltd.

60/61 Baizid Bostami Road, Nasirabad, Ctg.

2nd Company: Electrician (01/04/2008 to 05/05/2009).

Adhunic Paper Mills Ltd. Anarpura. Munshigonj.

3rd Company: Sr. Electrician (07-05-2009 to 20/07/2016).

Baizid Newsprint Mills Ltd.

60/61 Baizid Bostami Road, Nasirabad, Ctg.

4th Company: Sr. Technician (21/07/2016 to Continuing).

KSRM Billet Industries Ltd.

Company Location: Bora Kumira, Sitakunda, Chittagong.

Department: Electrical & Automation.

<u>Details / Responsibilities : </u>

- I. Working with troubleshooting and Schedule maintenance of Induction Furnace (IF) 30 Tons.
- II. Scrap transfer trolley maintenance and troubleshooting.
- III. Troubleshooting and Schedule Maintenance of EOT crane of the plant.(30MT-75MT) & Charging Crane (15 MT -15 MT) of the plant.
- IV. Working & Maintenance all kinds of AC motors Controlled by Star Delta, Forward Reverse, and DOL Stator.
- V. Reviewing in power Generator (1.5MW)
- VI. All Electrical Problem Troubleshooting and maintenance.
- VII. Monitoring & maintains Weekly & Monthly preventive Maintenances.
- VIII. Follow and communicate proper safety standards.

Education Qualification

Name Of	Institute	Group	Passing	Result	Board
Exam			Year		
SSC	Senbagh Govt. pilot High School	Business Studies	2000	2 nd Division	Comilla

Personal Qualification:

<u>Certification</u>	<u>Institute</u>	<u>From</u>	Passing Year	<u>Result</u>
Maintenance of Electrical Equipment	ВКТТС	1 st January to 30 th Jun	2015	A +
PLC Programmable Logic Control.	BKTTC	1 st July to 30 th December	2015	A +

Trading Summary:

Trading Title	Topic	Institute	Location	Year	Duration
ABC	Electrical	Bangladesh Govt.	Dhaka	2018	B"C"
Licenses		Licenses Board			
Recognition of prior learning (RPL)	National Skills Certificate -1 in Electrical	NIT	Chittagong	2015	Complete
(Ki Z)	Installation & maintenance, NTVQF.				

Personal Information:

Father's Name : Late. Md. Hanif Mother's Name : Rahima Khatun

Permanent Addres : Vill : North Mohammedpur, P.O : Senbagh,

P.S- Senbagh. Dist - Noakhali.

Present Address : Vill : New Rajapur, P.O : Kumira,

P.S- Sitakunda. Dist - Chittagong.

Date of Birth : 10-03-1984.

Sex : Male

Nationality : Bangladeshi (By Birth).

Marital Status : Married. Religion : Islam.

ID No : 19847518076000054

Blade Group : AB⁺

(Md. Ibrahim Khalil)